A Guide to the Fries Textile Plant Records, 1900-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series I: Company Files, 1908-1979
  - Shuford Mills, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Sides Woolen Mills, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Slip-Not Belting Corp., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Smokeless Fuel Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - Social Security Board, 1940 (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - Sonoco Products Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - L. Sonneborn Sons, Inc., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - Southern Conference of Human Relations in Industry, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - Southern Converting Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - Southern Electric Service, Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - Southern Nail Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - Southern Oxygen Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 27)
  - Southern Steel and Erecting Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 28)
  - Southwestern State Hospital, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 29)
  - Spaugh Paper Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 30)
  - Triumph Explosives, Inc., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 31)
  - Twin County Motor Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous "U", 1940 (Box 135, Folder 33)
  - United Fruit Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 34)
  - United Paper Company, Inc., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 35)
  - United States Gauge Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 36)
  - Universal Carloading Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 37)
  - Universal Winding Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 38)
  - C.L. Upchurch and Sons, Inc., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 39)
  - U.S. Government (folder 1 of 2), 1940 (Box 135, Folder 40)
  - U.S. Government (folder 2 of 2), 1940 (Box 135, Folder 41)
  - U.S. Gov't (Federal Power Comm.), 1940 (Box 135, Folder 42)
  - U.S. Ring Traveler Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous "V", 1940 (Box 135, Folder 44)
  - Valentine' Meat Juices Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 45)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 46)
  - Virginia Mfgr's Association, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 47)
  - Virginia Scrap Iron and Metal Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 48)
  - Va. State-Wide Safety Conference, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 49)
  - Virginia Tree Farm, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 50)
  - Va. Unemployment Compensation Comm., 1940 (Box 155, Folder 22)
  - Whitinsville Spinning Ring Co., 1940 (Box 135, Folder 52)
  - J.H. Windle and Company, 1940 (Box 135, Folder 53)
  - Miscellaneous "Y", 1940 (Box 135, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous "Z", 1940 (Box 135, Folder 55)
  - Old Notices (folder 1 of 2), 1925-1944 (Box 135, Folder 68)
  - Old Notices (folder 2 of 2), 1944-1961 (Box 135, Folder 69)
  - Factory Insurance, 1928-1949 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Sealed Mill Envelopes (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Maintence Records for Mill-Owned Homes, 1936-1959 (Box 59)
  - Election Returns Town of Fries, 1910 (Box 65)
  - Baptist Church, 1910-1914 (Box 65)
  - (titles?) Baptist Church, 1916-1918 (Box 129)
  - (Titles?) Baptist Church, 1919-1925 (Box 65)
  - Fries Baptist Church, 1931-1939 (Box 65)
  - W. House Freight Book showing where pkgs. Etc. are taken after receipt, 1935-1937 (Box 67)
  - Housing Repair Records, 1936-1963 (Box 67)
  - Rent Book, 1943-1955 (Box 67)
  - Addressograph-Multipgraph Proposal, 1957 (Box 68)
  - Cotton Buyer's Lightning Calculator Fries, VA, January 31, 1919 (Box 115)
  - Riegel Story Slide Deck, 1979 (Box 159)
  - Part 1 Cotton Dust: "Something In the Air", March 1980 (Box 136)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1901-1958
  - Corresp., 1933 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Corresp., 1934 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Corresp., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Corresp., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Corresp., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Corresp., 1907 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Corresp., 1905 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Corresp., 1910 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Corresp., 1911 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Corresp., 1912 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Corresp., 1913 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Corresp., 1914 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Corresp., 1915 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Corresp., 1916 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Corresp., 1917 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Corresp., 1918 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Corresp., 1918 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Corresp., 1918 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Corresp., 1919 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Corresp., 1921 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Corresp., 1922 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Corresp., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Corresp., 1923 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Corresp., 1924 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Corresp., 1924 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Corresp., 1925 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Corresp., 1925 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Corresp., 1926 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Corresp., 1931 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Corresp., 1913 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Corresp., 1914 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Corresp., 1915 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Corresp., 1917 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Corresp., 1919 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Corresp., 1923 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Corresp., 1925 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Corresp. (folder 1 of 2), 1926 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Corresp. (folder 2 of 2), 1926 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Corresp. (folder 1 of 2), 1927 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Corresp. (folder 2 of 2), 1927 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Corresp. (folder 1 of 2), 1928 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Corresp. (folder 2 of 2), 1928 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Corresp. (folder 1 of 2), 1929 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Corresp. (folder 2 of 2), 1929 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Corresp. (folder 1 of 2), 1930 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Corresp. (folder 2 of 2), 1930 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Corresp., 1931 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Corresp., 1932 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Corresp., 1932 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Corresp., 1932 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Corresp., 1932 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Corresp., 1933 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Corresp., 1934 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Sacco-Lowell Shops, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous S, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - F.H. Ross and Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Rock Hill Printing and Finishing Co, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Roberts Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Roanoke Engineering Sales Co., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Riegel Textile Corp., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Red Jacket Coal Corporation, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous R, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Progressive Machine Company, Inc., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Product Sales, Inc., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Pope and Talbot, Inc., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Pneumafil Corp., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Piedmont Mountain Freight Lines, Inc., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Joel S. Perkins and Sons, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Pearson, Hill, and Sullivan, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - W.M. Parsley, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Parks-Cramer Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous P., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Richard A. Owings Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Orkin Exterminating Company Inc., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Odell Mill Supply Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous O, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - North Electric Manufacturing Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Norris Brothers, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - National Cotton Council, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - National Carbide Co., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - National Cash Register Co., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Miscellaneous N, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - H.J. Murf and Co., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Mundy Motor Lines, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Morris Fur Co., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - J.W. Mortell Co., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Morgan Brothers Bag Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Monroe Calculating Machine Co., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Moisture Register Co., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Metron Instrument Company, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Babson Statistical Organization; J.S. Bache and Company, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Massapoag Mills Corporation, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - J.S. Bache and Company, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Babson Statistical Organization, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Babson Statistical Organization, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Leslie Evans and Company, May 1942 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Leslie Evans and Company, April 1942 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - A.H. Bahnson, Treasurer [Washington Mills] (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Automobile Mutual Insurance Company; W.E. Austin Machinery Company, 1919 (Box 155, Folder 23)
  - William C. Atwater and Company; Automobile Mutual Insurance Company, 1921 (Box 155, Folder 24)
  - William C. Atwater and Comapny; Attalla Foundry and Machine Company, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Atlas Portland Cement Company; William C. Atwater and Company, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Atlas Portland Cement Company; William C. Atwater and Company, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Atlanta Textile Machinery Company; Atlas Portland Cement Company, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - The Atlas Portland Cement Company, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Eastern Malleable Iron Co., 1919 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Eastern Coal and Export Co; Eastern Iron and Metal Co, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Eastman Kodak Co; Eastern Coal and Export Corp., 1922 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - W.K. Early and Son; Early Electric Co., 1922 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Miscellaneous "A" (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Abbott Laboratories, July (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Abington Textile Machinery Works, September- November (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Acme Mfg. and Gasket Co., April 1941- August 1942 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Acme Steel Company, January- September (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Albury and Co. Inc., September- November (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - A. S. Aloe Company, April- August (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - American Cooperage and Steel Drum Co., March- June (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - The American Cotton Mfgr's Association (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - American Hawaiian S.S. Co., January (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - American-LaFrance Foamite Co., June- July (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - American Mfg. Company, April- October (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - American Paper Products, Inc., October- November (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Andrews Company, February- April (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Anson Mfg. Company, October- December (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Appalachian Elec. Power Co., August- November (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Application Letters, January- November (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Armstrong Cork Company, January- August (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Ashworth Bros, Inc., February- December (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Atlanta Brush Company, March- November (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Atlas Supply Co., January- October (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Automatic Sprinkler Cor. of America, August- November (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous "B" (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Babbitt Brothers, January- July (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Bahan Textile Machinery Co., February- November (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - The Bahnson Co., July- September (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Bahnson, Spaugh, Reid, Tulloch (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Barber-Colman Company, May- December (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Barrett-Cravens Co., May- July (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Batson Mfg. Co., March- May (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - J. T. Beaty Machine Works, May- September (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Belk's Stores, March- November (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Belknap Hardware and Mfg. Co., January- September (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Bemis Bro. Bag Co., January- July (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Benjamin's for Motors, January- April (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - A. C. Blancke and Co., September (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Booze Truck Lines, February- July (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Borne Scrymser Company, January- October (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Bowen-Hunter Bobbin Co., June-July (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Howard Bradshaw, March- December (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Breuer Elec. Mfg. Co., April- October (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Brown-Rogers-Dixon Co., March- August (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Butler Iron and Steel Co., March- November (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Department of Commerce, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous "C" (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Joe L. Carlton, January- March (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Carolina Bagging Co., March- April (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Carolina Frt. Carriers Corp., March (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - A. W. Cash Co., March (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Chain Belt Company, September (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Mr. F. H. Chamberlain (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Cinder Block, Inc., May- August (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Citizens Road League of Va., May- July (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Clark Tructractor, June- July (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Clinard Elec. Company, May (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Continental Paper Grading Company, November- December (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Corn Products Sales Co., January- November (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Cotton Textile Institute, Inc., February- August (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Cross Cotton Mills Co., November- December (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Curtis and Marble Machine Co., January- November (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous D, March- December (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Defense Supplies Corporation, December (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Dillard Paper Company, February- July (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - S. R. Dixon Lumber Co., June- September (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - The C. B Dolge Company, September- December (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Drake Corporation (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Draper Corporation (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - The Dresco Company, Inc., January (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - D. S. Engineering Co., September- November (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - E. I. Dupont de Nemours and Co., March- November (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Miscellaneous "E", January- November (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Eastern Motor Express Co, August- December (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Esteve Bros. and Co., Inc., October (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Miscellaneous "F" (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Factory Insurance Association, January- November (Box 155, Folder 25)
  - Fibre Specialty Mfg. Co, July- September (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - First National Bank, November- December (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Fields Mfg. Co. (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Michael Flynn Mfg. Co., April- December (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Fog Nozzle Company, February (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - J. W. Fraser Company (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - Friedman Bros., March- August (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - Miscellaneous "G" (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - A. F. Gallun and Sons Corp., April- December (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - General Electric Supply Co., April- November (Box 40, Folder 85)
  - Gill Leather Company (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - Gittlin Charlotte Bag Co., September- December (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - Golden Supply Co., February- July (Box 40, Folder 88)
  - Grayson County, March- December (Box 40, Folder 89)
  - Greensboro Loom Reed Co., February (Box 40, Folder 90)
  - Green Tweed Comapny, May- June (Box 40, Folder 91)
  - Grinnell Company, February- November (Box 40, Folder 92)
  - Hobert N. Grubb, February- November (Box 40, Folder 93)
  - Miscellaneous "H" (Box 40, Folder 94)
  - N. B. Handy Company, January- October (Box 40, Folder 95)
  - H. and P. Spool and Bobbin Co., January (Box 40, Folder 96)
  - Chas. Harmon and Co., January- June (Box 40, Folder 97)
  - Hercules Powder Company, March- November (Box 40, Folder 98)
  - Hospital Savings Association, March- December (Box 40, Folder 99)
  - Miscellaneous "I", February- December (Box 40, Folder 100)
  - Industrial Supply Co., February- July (Box 40, Folder 101)
  - Miscellaneous "J" (Box 40, Folder 102)
  - E. H. Jacobs Mfg. Co., April- November (Box 40, Folder 103)
  - Jefferson Machine Tool Co, May- June (Box 40, Folder 104)
  - Jeffrey Mfg. Co., June- July (Box 40, Folder 105)
  - Johannesen Elec. Co, Inc., May- July (Box 40, Folder 106)
  - Miscellaneous "K", February- December (Box 40, Folder 107)
  - Keasbey and Mattison Company, August (Box 40, Folder 108)
  - Killingly Worsted Mills, October- December (Box 40, Folder 109)
  - Kimmel Machinery Co., Inc., February- July (Box 40, Folder 110)
  - Miscellaneous "L" (Box 40, Folder 111)
  - Lambeth Products Corp., April (Box 40, Folder 112)
  - Leckie Coal Co, Inc., June- November (Box 40, Folder 113)
  - Leslie, Evans and Co., December 1942 (Box 40, Folder 114)
  - Leslie, Evans and Co., November 1942 (Box 40, Folder 115)
  - Leslie, Evans and Company, October 1942 (Box 40, Folder 116)
  - Leslie Evans and Co, September 1942 (Box 40, Folder 117)
  - Leslie, Evans and Company, August 1942 (Box 40, Folder 118)
  - Avondale Mills, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Automatic Transportation Company, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Automatic Transportation Company, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Austin-Western Road Machinery Company, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Automatic Sprinkler Company of America; Automatic Transportation Company, 1919 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Automatic Refrigerating Company, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Austin-Western Road Machinery Company, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Austin-Western Road Machinery Company, 1919 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Automobile Mutual Insurance Company; Austin-Western Road Machinery Company, 1920 (Box 155, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous L., 1947 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Oliver D. Landis; Leckie Coal Company, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lee Telephone Co., 1947 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Leslie and Company, January 1947 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Leslie and Company, February 1947 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Leslie and Company, March 1947 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Leslie and Company, April 1947 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Leslie and Company, May 1947 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Leslie and Company, June 1947 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Leslie and Company, July 1947 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Leslie and Company, August 1947 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Leslie and Company, September 1947 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Leslie and Company, October 1947 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Leslie and Company, November 1947 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Leslie and Company, December 1947 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Levin Brothers; Wilson Lewith Machinery Corp, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Linde Air Products Company; Lineberry Foundry and Machine Co., 1947 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - H.F. Livermore Company; Lynchburg Iron and Metal Company, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Lynchburg Rendering Co.; Lynchburg Foundry Co., 1947 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous "L", 1941 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - T. Holt Laird, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Lambeth Electric Supply Co., 1941 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - The Leadite Co., 1941 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Leckie Coal Company, Inc., 1941 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - W.S. Lee Engineering Corporation, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Leslie Evans and Co., October 1941 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Leslie Evans and Co., November 1941 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Leslie, Evans and Company, December 1941 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Lynchburg Rendering Company, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - A. Lyons and Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Adell Mill Supply Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Eastman Kodak Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Electric Furnace Corp., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Electric Service and Sales, Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Ely Walker Dry Goods Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Esso Standard Oil Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - ET and WNC Transportation, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous F, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Factory Insurance Association, 1956 (Box 155, Folder 27)
  - Ferguson Gear Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - The First National Bank of Memphis, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Fries High School, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Fisher Governor Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Fisher Manufacturing Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Fiske-Carter Construction Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Flat-Top Fuel Company, Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - The Flintkote Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - FX Lab Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous G, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Gardner-Denver Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - General Motors Lines, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Clair H. Gingher and Son, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Gossett Machine Works Inc, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - WW Grainger, Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Graybar Electric Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Mr Bob Green, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Griggs Trucking Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Miscellaneous H, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Halls Textile Machinery Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Harper Motor Lines, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - The Hawkins-Hamilton Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - T.W. Heath and Sons, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Hennis Freight Line Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Hermas Machine Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - John Hetherington and Sons, Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - R.E.L. Holt Jr. and Associates Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Hospital Savings Association of North Carolina, Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Miscellaneous "I", 1956 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Ingersoll Rand Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Intermountain Telephone Co. (Bristol, VA), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Internal Revenue, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Island Coal Sales Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Miscellaneous "J", 1956 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Mr. Henry Jarvis, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Jenkins Metal Shops, Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Joel S. Perkins and Son, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Miscellaneous "K", 1956 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Keasbey and Mattison Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - The Keever Starch Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - The Kendall Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Kendall Mills, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - W.A. Kennedy, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Kester Machinery Company, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Walter Kidde and Co. Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Kingsport Electric Co, Inc., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Peter Knowles, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Joseph Kopperman and Sons, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Miscellaneous "L", 1956 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Oliver D. Landis, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Senator Floyd Landreth, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - Leslie and Co, January 1956 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Leslie and Co, February 1956 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Leslie and Co, March 1956 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Leslie and Co, April 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Leslie and Co (May), 1956 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Leslie and Co (June), 1956 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Leslie and Co, July 1956 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Leslie and Co, August 1956 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Leslie and Co, September 1956 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Leslie and Co, October 1956 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Leslie and Co, November 1956 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Leslie and Co, December 1956 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - H.F. Livermore Corp., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Livingston and Haven, Inc., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - J.E. Lonergan Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Loom Service Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Lowell Shuttle Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Lyman Printing and Finishing Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Lynchburg Foundry Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Lynchburg Iron and Metal Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous "Mc", 1956 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - McDonough Power and Equipment Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1956 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Machinecraft, Inc., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Mail Order, Inc., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Malone Freight Lines, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Manning, Maxwell and Moore, Inc., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Mantor-Gaulin Mfg. Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - The Martindale Electric Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Martinsville Office Supply Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Maryland Casualty Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - The Mason and Dixon Lines, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Co. of America, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Metron Instrument Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Monroe Calculating Machine Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Mundy Motor Lines, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 36)